Finding Aid for Kelsey Museum of Archaeology papers 1890-1987
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Francis Willey Kelsey papers, 1890-1927; 65.5 linear feet
  - Correspondence
    - L Correspondence
      - Longyear, Mary Beecher, 1919-1925; 3 folders
        - 1921-1925 (Box 21, Folder 14)
      - Lorch, Emil, 1917-1922; 1925 (Box 21, Folder 15)
      - Lord, Louis E., 1913; 1915-1923 (Box 21, Folder 16)
      - Lowe, E.A., 1923; 1925-1926 (Box 21, Folder 17)
      - Lyman, R.L., 1914-1917 (Box 21, Folder 18)
      - Lythgoe, Albert M., 1912-1921; 1923 (Box 21, Folder 19)
      - General Correspondence - L, undated; 2 folders
        - La-Le (Box 22, Folder 1)
        - Li-Ly (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - M Correspondence
      - Magoffin, Ralph V.D.
        - 1907, 1913-1920 (Box 22, Folder 3)
        - 1921-1926 (Box 22, Folder 4)
        - 1923-1924 (Box 22, Folder 5)
        - 1925-1926 (Box 22, Folder 6)
      - Maloney, William J.M.A., 1923; 1926-1927 (Box 22, Folder 7)
      - Marsh, Edward C., 1921-1922 (Box 22, Folder 8)
      - McAllister, Tom, 1917-1918 (Box 22, Folder 9)
      - McCartney, Eugene S., 1916; 1922-1924; 1925-1926 (Box 22, Folder 10)
      - McClure, James G.K., 1903; 1911-1924; 1926-1927 (Box 22, Folder 11)
      - McCormick, Cyrus H.M., 1902; 1911; 1924; 1926 (Box 23, Folder 1)
      - McCormick, Frederick, 1913-1916 (Box 23, Folder 2)
      - Mead, William Rutherford, 1913-1919; 1924; 1926 (Box 23, Folder 3)
      - Meinecke, Bruno, 1922-1926 (Box 23, Folder 4)
      - Merriam, John C., 1921-1925 (Box 23, Folder 5)
      - Merrill, John E., 1921-1923; 1925-1926 (Box 23, Folder 6)
      - Meusel, H., 1908; 1912-1914 (Box 23, Folder 7)
      - Miller, Edwin L., 1913-1916; 1919; 1923; 1926 (Box 23, Folder 8)
      - Miller, Walter, 1911-1918; 1923-1925 (Box 23, Folder 9)
      - Montgomery, James A., 1921-1923 (Box 23, Folder 10)
      - Moore, Charles, 1910-1922
        - 1910-1915 (Box 23, Folder 11)
        - 1916-1917 (Box 23, Folder 12)
        - 1918-1923 (Box 23, Folder 13)
      - More, Paul E., 1909-1913 (Box 24, Folder 1)
      - Morey, Charles
        - 1912-1915, 2 folders (Box 24, Folder 2)
        - 1912-1915, 2 folders (Box 24, Folder 3)
        - 1918-1922 (Box 24, Folder 4)
      - Morgan, J. Pierpont, 1915-1918; 1923-1927 (Box 24, Folder 5)
      - Moses, Lionel, 1915-1919 (Box 24, Folder 6)
      - Murphy, William H., 1914-1926
        - 1914-1919 (Box 24, Folder 7)
        - 1920-1926 (Box 24, Folder 8)
      - General Correspondence - M, undated
        - Ma (Box 24, Folder 9)
        - Mc-Me (Box 24, Folder 10)
        - Mi-My (Box 24, Folder 11)
    - N Correspondence
      - Newberry, Truman H., 1921-1922 (Box 25, Folder 1)
      - Nichole, James H., 1920-1921 (Box 25, Folder 2)
      - Norton, Ellen W., 1920-1922 (Box 25, Folder 3)
      - Norton, Richard
        - 1912-1916 (Box 25, Folder 3)
        - 1916-1918, 1924 (Box 25, Folder 5)
      - General Correspondence - N, undated (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - O Correspondence
      - Oldfather, W.A., 1913; 1922-1924 (Box 25, Folder 7)
      - Osband, Marna, 1913-1917; 1919 (Box 25, Folder 8)
      - Osborn, Chase S., 1909-1910; 1914; 1922-1923 (Box 25, Folder 9)
      - General Correspondence - O, undated (Box 25, Folder 10)
    - P Correspondence
      - Peabody, Charles, 1919-1923 (Box 25, Folder 11)
      - Pearl, Mary J., 1924-1927 (Box 25, Folder 12)
      - Peet, William W., 1919-1924 (Box 25, Folder 13)
      - Pendleton, Catherine B., 1923-1927; 2 folders
        - 1923-1925 (Box 25, Folder 14)
        - 1926-1927 (Box 25, Folder 15)
      - Pine, John B., 1917-1919; 1922 (Box 26, Folder 1)
      - Plimpton, George A., 1912-1923 (Box 26, Folder 2)
      - Post, Edwin, 1903; 1908; 1910-1914; 1916-1917; 1923; 1926 (Box 26, Folder 3)
      - Preisigke, Fredrich, 1923-1924 (Box 26, Folder 4)
      - Putnam, George H.
        - 1915-1918 (Box 26, Folder 5)
        - 1921-1922 (Box 26, Folder 6)
        - 1923-1927 (Box 26, Folder 7)
      - General Correspondence - P, undated
        - Pa (Box 26, Folder 8)
        - Pe-Pl (Box 26, Folder 9)
        - Po-Pu (Box 26, Folder 10)
    - Q Correspondence
      - General Correspondence - Q, undated (Box 26, Folder 11)
    - R Correspondence
      - Ramsay, William C.
        - 1910-1912, 1916-1919 (Box 27, Folder 1)
        - 1920-1926 (Box 27, Folder 2)
      - Rand, E.K., 1913-1926
        - 1913-1916 (Box 27, Folder 3)
        - 1917-1926 (Box 27, Folder 4)
      - Read, Hercules, 1916-1918 (Box 27, Folder 5)
      - Reeves, Jesse S., 1913; 1919-1926 (Box 27, Folder 6)
      - Reid, James S., 1910-1911; 1913-1920; 1923 (Box 27, Folder 7)
      - Rhees, Rush, 1914; 1918; 1920; 1925-1926 (Box 27, Folder 8)
      - Rhodes, Katherine N., 1919-1921 (Box 27, Folder 9)
      - Richter, Gisela, 1915-1916; 1921-1923; 1925-1926 (Box 27, Folder 10)
      - Robbins, Frank E.
        - 1913, 1919-1923 (Box 27, Folder 11)
        - 1924-1927 (Box 27, Folder 12)
      - Robinson, David M., 1910-1914; 1916-1917; 1921 (Box 28, Folder 1)
      - Robinson, Edward, 1913-1915; 1922-1923 (Box 28, Folder 2)
      - Robinson, George, 1903; 1911-1914; 1916 (Box 28, Folder 3)
      - Rodenwaldt, G., 1924-1927 (Box 28, Folder 4)
      - Rolfe, John C., 1901; 1906; 1910-1917; 1919; 1922-1925 (Box 28, Folder 5)
      - Rowe, Alan, 1925; 1927 (Box 28, Folder 6)
      - Russ, E.B., 1910-1914 (Box 28, Folder 7)
      - Russel, John R.
        - 1911, 1917-1919 (Box 28, Folder 8)
        - 1920-1925, 1927 (Box 28, Folder 9)
      - Rust, Isabel, 1922-1923; 1926 (Box 28, Folder 10)
      - General Correspondence - R, undated
        - Ra-Ri (Box 28, Folder 11)
        - Ro-Ru (Box 28, Folder 12)
    - S Correspondence
      - Sabin, Frances E., 1913-1914; 1920-1923; 1926 (Box 29, Folder 1)
      - Sage, Russell (Mrs.), 1910-1911 (Box 29, Folder 2)
      - Sanders, Henry A., 1913-1927
        - 1913-1914 (Box 29, Folder 3)
        - 1915 (Box 29, Folder 4)
        - 1916 (Box 29, Folder 5)
        - 1917-1920 (Box 29, Folder 6)
        - 1921-1922 (Box 29, Folder 7)
        - 1923-1924 (Box 29, Folder 8)
        - 1925-1927 (Box 29, Folder 9)
      - Schmidt, Carl, 1925-1927 (Box 30, Folder 1)
      - Schmidt, Otto L., 1923-1924 (Box 30, Folder 2)
      - Scott, Fred N., 1913-1917; 1919-1920; 1922-1923; 1925-1926 (Box 30, Folder 3)
      - Scott, James Brown
        - 1911, 1916; 1919-1922 (Box 30, Folder 4)
        - 1923-1926 (Box 30, Folder 5)
      - Sedgewick, Ellery, 1913-1922; 1924-1925 (Box 30, Folder 6)
      - Shipley, F. W.
        - 1913 (Box 30, Folder 7)
        - 1914-1915 (Box 30, Folder 8)
        - 1916-1917, 3 folders (Box 30, Folder 9)
        - 1918-1923, 1925-1926 (Box 30, Folder 10)
      - Shorey, Paul, 1910-1912; 1915-1917; 1923; 1925-1926 (Box 30, Folder 11)
      - Sihler, Ernest G., 1921-1923; 1925-1926 (Box 30, Folder 12)
      - Smith, Frederick L., 1918-1919 (Box 30, Folder 13)
      - Snyder, Harry J., 1920-1922 (Box 30, Folder 14)
      - Spaulding, Oliver L.
        - 1914-1916, 1919 (Box 31, Folder 1)
        - 1920-1921 (Box 31, Folder 2)
        - 1922-1926 (Box 31, Folder 3)
      - Springer, Frank., 1917-1923; 1926-1929; 1921-1927 (Box 31, Folder 4)
      - Stearns, Alfred E., 1923-1926 (Box 31, Folder 5)
      - Stearns, Frederick K., 1909; 1914-1915; 1918; 1922-1924 (Box 31, Folder 6)
        (includes his son, Frederick K. Stearns 1924)
      - Stearns, Wallace, 1911-1912; 1916-1918 (Box 31, Folder 7)
      - Steinbach, Emelie, 1913-1915; 1917-1919; 1921; 1923; 1926 (Box 31, Folder 8)
      - Stevens, Graham P., 1915-1927
        - 1915-1919 (Box 31, Folder 9)
        - 1920-1923 (Box 31, Folder 10)
        - 1925-1927 (Box 31, Folder 11)
      - Stout, Selatle E., 1916; 1922-1923; 1926-1927 (Box 31, Folder 12)
      - Swain, George
        - 1913-1915 (Box 32, Folder 1)
        - 1916-1917, 1919-1920 (Box 32, Folder 2)
        - 1921-1924, 1926 (Box 32, Folder 3)
        - Sa-Sc (Box 32, Folder 4)
        - Se-Sh (Box 32, Folder 5)
        - Si-So (Box 32, Folder 6)
        - Sp-Ste (Box 32, Folder 7)
        - Sti-Sw (Box 32, Folder 8)
    - T Correspondence
      - Tanner, Rollin H., 1917; 1923-1926 (Box 33, Folder 1)
      - Thurston, Ada, 1918-1919 (Box 33, Folder 2)
      - Tiggert, J.J., 1922-1923; 1926 (Box 33, Folder 3)
      - Tonapetean, P., 1914-1917 (Box 33, Folder 4)
      - Torrey, Charles C., 1913; 1915-1917; 1926 (Box 33, Folder 5)
      - Trowbridge, Breck, 1913; 1917; 1920 (Box 33, Folder 6)
      - Trowbridge, Stephen, 1920-1922 (Box 33, Folder 7)
      - General Correspondence - T, undated (Box 33, Folder 8)
    - U Correspondence
      - Ullman, B.L., 1916; 1918-1919; 1921-1924 (Box 33, Folder 9)
      - General Correspondence - U, undated (Box 33, Folder 10)
    - V Correspondence
      - Valentiner, W.R., 1925-1926 (Box 33, Folder 11)
      - Van Buren, Albert W., 1913-1916; 1920-1923 (Box 33, Folder 12)
      - Van Deman, Esther, 1906; 1910-1913; 1921; 1924-1926 (Box 33, Folder 13)
      - Van Den Ven, Paul, 1915-1916 (Box 33, Folder 14)
      - Van Hoesen, Henry B., 1915-1916; 1925-1927 (Box 33, Folder 15)
      - Van Horne, William, 1912; 1914-1915 (Box 34, Folder 1)
      - Vaughn, V.C., 1911-1914; 1922-1923 (Box 34, Folder 2)
      - Vignon, Paul, 1915-1917; 1919 (Box 34, Folder 3)
      - General Correspondence - V, undated (Box 34, Folder 4)
    - W Correspondence
      - Wace, A.J.B., 1923-1924 (Box 34, Folder 5)
      - Walcott, Charles
        - 1913-1916 (Box 34, Folder 6)
        - 1918-1923 (Box 34, Folder 7)
      - Waldo, Lewis, 1918-1919 (Box 34, Folder 8)
      - Walker, Bryant, 1914; 1922; 1925-1926 (Box 34, Folder 9)
      - Wallace, E. B., 1920-1923; 1925-1927 (Box 34, Folder 10)
      - Waltzing, Jean-Pierre, 1908; 1910-1912; 1914-1915; 1926-1927 (Box 34, Folder 11)
      - Warburg, Paul, 1908; 1911-1914; 1916-1918; 1923 (Box 34, Folder 12)
      - Warner, Langdon, 1912; 1913-1915; 1922-1923 (Box 34, Folder 13)
      - Waterman, Leroy, 1914-1927 (Box 34, Folder 14)
      - Webber, Oscar, 1923-1927 (Box 35, Folder 1)
      - Webber, Richard, 1924-1927 (Box 35, Folder 2)
      - Weller, Charles, 1913-1914; 1916; 1921-1922 (Box 35, Folder 3)
      - Wenley, R. M., 1901; 1910-1919; 1921-1926 (Box 35, Folder 4)
      - West, Andrew F.
        - 1913-1917 (Box 35, Folder 5)
        - 1918-1919, 1921-1922 (Box 35, Folder 6)
        - 1923-1927 (Box 35, Folder 7)
      - Westermann, W. L., 1918-1927
        - 1913-1917 (Box 35, Folder 8)
        - 1918-1921 (Box 35, Folder 9)
        - 1911-1923 (Box 35, Folder 10)
      - Wetmore, M. N., 1917; 1921-1925 (Box 35, Folder 11)
      - White, Dorrence, 1923-1927 (Box 35, Folder 12)
      - White, Edward C., 1916; 1918-1919; 1921-1922; 1925-1926 (Box 35, Folder 13)
      - White, H. G. Evelyn, 1920-1921 (Box 35, Folder 14)
      - White, Lee A., 1917; 1922-1925 (Box 35, Folder 15)
      - White, Peter, 1905-1908 (Box 35, Folder 16)
      - Whitney, A. S., 1913-1914; 1916-1919; 1921; 1923; 1926 (Box 35, Folder 17)
      - Wilgus, H. L., 1917-1922; 1924-1926 (Box 36, Folder 1)
      - Williams, Charles R., 1911-1915; 1920-1922; 1925 (Box 36, Folder 2)
      - Williams, George, 1910-1912; 1914 (Box 36, Folder 3)
      - Wilson, Harry L., 1913-1914 (Box 36, Folder 4)
        (includes Mrs. Wilson)
      - Wilson, Woodrow, 1913; 1915 (Box 36, Folder 5)
      - Wiltsie, Charles H.
        - 1911-1915 (Box 36, Folder 6)
        - 1919-1921 (Box 36, Folder 7)
        - 1924-1926 (Box 36, Folder 8)
      - Winter, John G., 1920-1921 (Box 36, Folder 9)
      - Woodward, Robert S., 1909-1914; 1918 (Box 36, Folder 10)
        - 1911-1914, 1922 (Box 36, Folder 11)
        - 1923-1924 (Box 36, Folder 12)
      - Worrell, W. H., 1913-1927; 9 folders
        - 1913-1914 (Box 37, Folder 1)
        - 1915 (Box 37, Folder 2)
        - 1916 (Box 37, Folder 3)
        - 1917 (Box 37, Folder 4)
        - 1918 (Box 37, Folder 5)
        - 1919 (Box 37, Folder 6)
        - 1920-1921 (Box 37, Folder 7)
        - 1922-1923 (Box 37, Folder 8)
        - 1924-1927 (Box 37, Folder 9)
      - Wright, Herbert F., 1923-1926 (Box 37, Folder 10)
      - Wulfing, John Max, 1921-1927; 4 folders
        - 1921-1922 (Box 38, Folder 1)
        - 1923 (Box 38, Folder 2)
        - 1924 (Box 38, Folder 3)
        - 1925-1927 (Box 38, Folder 4)
      - General Correspondence - W, undated; 4 folders
        - Wa (Box 38, Folder 5)
        - We-Wh (Box 38, Folder 6)
        - Wi (Box 38, Folder 7)
        - Wo-Wy (Box 38, Folder 8)
    - Y Correspondence
      - Yahuda, A. S., 1925-1926 (Box 38, Folder 9)
      - Yeames, Herbert, 1911-1917; 1925-1926 (Box 38, Folder 10)
      - General Correspondence - Y-Z, undated
        - Y (Box 38, Folder 11)
        - Z (Box 38, Folder 12)
    - Private Correspondence
      - American Express Company, N.Y., 1925 (Box 39, Folder 1)
      - Bishop, W. W., 1926 (Box 39, Folder 2)
      - Carus, Paul (Mrs.), 1922 (Box 39, Folder 3)
      - Eastman, Sidney C., 1920; 1923-1924 (Box 39, Folder 4)
      - Griffith, A. H., 1912 (Box 39, Folder 5)
      - Kahn, Albert H., 1911 (Box 39, Folder 6)
      - Mygind, Holger, 1922 (Box 39, Folder 7)
      - Pease, Arthur S., 1913 (Box 39, Folder 8)
      - Robinson, Edward, 1921 (Box 39, Folder 9)
      - Spitzer, Carl B., 1913 (Box 39, Folder 10)
      - Fr. Vester & Company, 1921; 1923 (Box 39, Folder 11)
      - Wormser, Moritz, 1922 (Box 39, Folder 12)
      - "Giro" at Pompeii, 1895 (Box 39, Folder 13)
  - Professional Organizations and Meetings
    - American Anthropological Association., 1906; 1920; 1922-1923 (Box 40, Folder 1)
    - American Association of University Professors, 1916-1917; 1920; 1924 (Box 40, Folder 2)
    - Ann Arbor Civic Association, 1914-1917 (Box 40, Folder 3)
    - Archaeological Institute of America
      - Documents and Papers
        - Certified Articles of Incorporation, January 3, 1911 (Box 40, Folder 4)
        - Legal papers, 1909-1910 (Box 40, Folder 5)
        - Endowment-Monographs, 1908; 1909; 1912; 1914 (Box 40, Folder 6)
        - Miscellaneous Papers, 1892; 1907-1918 (Box 40, Folder 7)
        - Miscellaneous Pamphlets, undated (Box 40, Folder 8)
      - Officers. Presidents
        - White, John Williams
          - 1901-1902 (Box 40, Folder 9)
          - 1902-1903, 1908; 1909 (Box 40, Folder 10)
        - Seymour, Thomas, 1903-1908
          - undated, 1903-1904 (Box 41, Folder 1)
          - circa 1905-1906 (Box 41, Folder 2)
          - 1907-1908 (Box 41, Folder 3)
        - Wilson, Harry L., 1895; 1898; 1913 (Box 41, Folder 4)
      - Treasurer Accounts
        - 1908 (Box 41, Folder 5)
        - 1909 (Box 41, Folder 6)
        - 1910, 1912 (Box 41, Folder 7)
      - Accounts
        - Jones, W. T. S., 1911 (Box 41, Folder 8)
        - Marston, F. C., 1912 (Box 41, Folder 9)
        - Nairns, F. B., 1910-1911
        - Western Union, 1911 (Box 41, Folder 1)
        - Vouchers
          - Duplicate
            - 1902-1905 (Box 42, Folder 1)
            - 1906-1907 (Box 42, Folder 2)
          - President, 1910 (Box 42, Folder 3)
          - Associate Secretaries and Secretaries, 1909-1910 (Box 42, Folder 4)
          - Miscellaneous, 1909-1910 (Box 42, Folder 5)
        - Account Ledger, 1910-1911 (Box 42, Folder 6)
      - Meetings
        - 1903-1910 (Box 42, Folder 7)
        - 1911-1917, 1921-1922 (Box 42, Folder 8)
        - Circulars, 1902-1906; 1910 (Box 42, Folder 9)
      - Bulletin of the Archaeological Institute of America, 1910-1919 (Box 43)
      - Minutes of the Meetings of the Council, 1907-1912 (Box 43)
      - Reports
        - Reports of the Presidents, 1908-1912; 1915; 1917 (Box 43)
        - Third Annual Report of the General Secretary, 1911 (Box 43)
        - Reports of the Officers, 1912-1913 (Box 43)
        - Annual Report of the Managing Committee of the American School of Classical Studies in Rome, 1911-1912 (Box 43)
        - Annual Report of the Managing Committee of the American School of Classical Studies at Athens, 1908 (Box 43)
        - Annual Report of the Managing Committee the Mediaeval and Renaissance Studies, 1911-1912 (Box 43)
        - The Excavations at Cyrene
          - First Campaign, 1910-1911 (Box 43)
          - Preliminary Reports by Richard Norton, Joseph C., Hoppin, Charles 0. Curtis and A. F. S. Sladden, 1911 (Box 43)
      - Directory of the Archaeological Institute of America, 1910-1911; 1916-1917 (Box 43)
      - Annual Statements, 1909-1912; 2 folders (Box 43)
      - Publications
        - American Journal of Archaeology, 1899 (Box 43)
        - Extracts from the Bulletins of the A.I.A, undated (Box 43)
    - August Mau Memorial
      - Photograph, Reprint of article re: Memorial, foreign circular, undated (Box 44, Folder 1)
      - Pompeii Paintings, 1901-1902; 1907; 1909-1911 (Box 44, Folder 2)
      - Contributions
        - 1909-1910 (Box 44, Folder 3)
        - 1910, 1914 (Box 44, Folder 4)
      - Accounts, Letters, 1909-1911 (Box 44, Folder 5)
      - Amelung, Walter and Dodge, Cleveland H., 1910-1913 (Box 44, Folder 6)
      - Delbrueck, R., 1910-1914 (Box 44, Folder 7)
      - Warren, Langford H., 1910-1911 (Box 44, Folder 8)
    - The Authors' Club
      - Miscellaneous Papers, 1910-1927 (Box 44, Folder 9)
      - Reports, 1912-1927 (Box 44, Folder 10)
    - Classical Association of the Middle West and South
      - Miscellaneous Papers
        - 1904-1905 (Box 44, Folder 11)
        - 1906-1907, 1914-1917 (Box 44, Folder 12)
      - Barber, Grove, Miscellaneous Conference Programs, 1906-1917 (Box 44, Folder 13)
      - Commission of Nine, 1908-1909 (Box 44, Folder 14)
      - Classical Journal and Classical Philology, 1905-1906 (Box 44, Folder 15)
    - Michigan Schoolmasters' Club, 1895; 1908; 1911-1912; 1925-1927 (Box 45, Folder 1)
    - National Institute of Social Sciences, 1914-1915; 1917-1919 (Box 45, Folder 2)
    - Science Service, 1926 (Box 45, Folder 3)
    - Societies and Organizations, undated
      - A (Box 45, Folder 4)
      - B-M (Box 45, Folder 5)
      - N-W (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - General Business Correspondence
    - Companies
      - American Express Company, 1924-1927 (Box 46, Folder 1)
      - American Type Foundry Company, 1909-1912 (Box 46, Folder 2)
      - Brown, Shipley & Company, 1919-1921; 1924-1926 (Box 46, Folder 3)
      - Cushing & Company, 1909-1919; 9 folders
        - 1909-1911 (Box 46, Folder 4)
        - 1912 (Box 46, Folder 5)
        - 1913 (Box 46, Folder 6)
        - 1914 (Box 46, Folder 7)
        - 1915 (Box 46, Folder 8)
        - 1916 (Box 46, Folder 9)
        - 1917 (Box 46, Folder 10)
        - 1918 (Box 46, Folder 11)
        - 1919 (Box 46, Folder 12)
      - Detroit Trust Company, 1920-1921 (Box 46, Folder 13)
      - First and Old Detroit National Bank, 1921 (Box 46, Folder 14)
      - M. 0. Henning, 1919-1924 (Box 47, Folder 1)
      - C. Leidich Travel Company, 1914-1915; 1919; 1924; 1926 (Box 47, Folder 2)
      - Martin Haller, 1922-1924 (Box 47, Folder 3)
      - National Photo Engraving Company, 1910-1922; 2 folders
        - 1910-1914 (Box 47, Folder 4)
        - 1915-1922 (Box 47, Folder 5)
      - L. L. Poates Engraving Company, 1896; 1913-1914; 1916-1918 (Box 47, Folder 6)
      - A. T. Thompson & Company, 1910-1911; 1913-1916; 1920 (Box 47, Folder 7)
      - Western Union Telegraph Company, 1901; 1913-1919; 1923 (Box 47, Folder 8)
      - General Correspondence, 2 folders
        - A-K (Box 47, Folder 9)
        - M-W (Box 47, Folder 10)
    - Booksellers
      - Th. Stauffer, 1909; 1911-1915 (Box 47, Folder 11)
      - G. E. Stechert & Company, 1911-1912; 1922-1923; 1925-1927 (Box 47, Folder 12)
      - General Correspondence (Box 47, Folder 13)
    - Foundations
      - Carnegie Foundation, 1919; 1922 (Box 47, Folder 14)
      - Foreign Research Fund, 1922-1924 (Box 47, Folder 15)
  - Educational Institutions
    - A.I.A. Schools
      - American School at Athens
        - A.I.A. Bulletins, 1913; 1921-1926; 10 folders (Box 48, Folder 1-10)
        - Auxiliary Fund Association, 1921-1922 (Box 48, Folder 11)
      - American School in China
        - Lung-Men and Rubbings (photos) Sent by Charles Freer, 1911 (Box 48, Folder 12)
        - General Business, 1912-1913 (Box 48, Folder 13)
        - Re: Establishment of School in China, 1913-1915 (Box 48, Folder 14)
        - American School in Peking. Oriental art, 1909-1913 (Box 48, Folder 15)
        - Walcott, Charles, 1912-1913 (Box 48, Folder 16)
      - American School in Jerusalem
        - Miscellaneous papers and articles, 1910; 1913-1915; 1926 (Box 49, Folder 1)
        - Miscellaneous catalogs and reports, 1900-1920 (Box 49, Folder 2)
        - Miscellaneous bulletins, 1920-1926 (Box 49, Folder 3)
      - American School of Classical Studies in Rome
        - Reports
          - General, 1902-1903; 1904-1908; 1910-1911; 1913-1925 (Box 50, Folder 4)
          - Managing Committee, 1897-1898 (Box 50, Folder 1)
          - Executive Committee, 1914-1919 (Box 50, Folder 2)
          - Trustee, 1913-1919 (Box 50, Folder 3)
        - West, Andrew, 1902-1914; 3 folders
          - 1902-1909 (Box 50, Folder 4)
          - 1910-1911 (Box 50, Folder 5)
          - 1912-1914 (Box 50, Folder 6)
        - Carter, Jesse, 1902-1912; 3 folders (Box 50, Folder 7)
          - 1902-1907 (Box 50, Folder 7)
          - 1908-1909 (Box 50, Folder 8)
          - 1910-1912 (Box 50, Folder 9)
        - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1911-1912 (Box 50, Folder 10)
        - Contracts and Estimates, 1915 (Box 51, Folder 1)
        - Report to Trustees: construction, April-May 1915 (Box 51, Folder 2)
        - Pictures and map, 1915 (Box 51, Folder 3)
        - U. of M. contributions
          - 1900-1906 (Box 51, Folder 4)
          - 1913-1914 (Box 51, Folder 5)
        - Students
          - 1905-1906, 1907-1909 (Box 51, Folder 6)
          - 1922-1923 (Box 51, Folder 7)
        - Fellowships
          - 1902-1908 (Box 51, Folder 8)
          - 1913-1917 (Box 51, Folder 9)
        - Circulars, 1895-1911 (Box 51, Folder 10)
        - Miscellaneous papers, 1911-1919; 2 folders
          - 1911-1912 (Box 51, Folder 11)
          - 1913-1919 (Box 51, Folder 12)
        - Prospectus; Miscellaneous Reports, 1908-1913 (Box 51, Folder 13)
        - Miscellaneous material, 1911-1915 (Box 52, Folder 1)
      - American School in Santa Fe
        - Miscellaneous papers, 1912-1914; 2 folders
          - 1912-1914 (Box 51, Folder 2)
          - 1913-1914 (Box 51, Folder 3)
        - Bulletins, reports, papers, 1908-1917 (Box 52, Folder 5)
        - Catalogue of Deane Collection, undated (Box 52, Folder 6)
          (photographs)
    - University of Michigan
      - Alumni Association
        - Shaw, W. B., 1913; 1916; 1920-1926 (Box 53, Folder 1)
      - Board of Regents
        - Miscellaneous papers, 1906-1919 (Box 53, Folder 2)
        - Hubbard, Lucius L., 1913-1914; 1916; 1918; 1920; 1922-1923 (Box 53, Folder 3)
      - Buildings and Grounds
        - Flook, L. R. and Pardon, E. C., 1913; 1916-1919 (Box 53, Folder 4)
      - Clubs and Associations
        - Classical Club
          - Constitution; Installation; copies of Latine, undated (Box 53, Folder 5)
          - Membership, 1920-1921 (Box 53, Folder 6)
          - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1918-1921; 1924 (Box 53, Folder 7)
          - Statements; Checkbooks, 1917-1918 (Box 53, Folder 8)
          - Miscellaneous financial statements, 1916-1921 (Box 53, Folder 9)
          - Minutes, 1914-1917 (Box 53, Folder 10)
          - Treasurer's reports, 1915-1917 (Box 53, Folder 11)
          - Club programs, suggestions, photos and notes, undated (Box 53, Folder 12)
          - Classics and classical plays, undated (Box 53, Folder 13)
        - Club Plays
          - The Menaechmi
            - 1890 (Box 54, Folder 1)
            - Letters, miscellaneous material, costumes, 1916 (Box 54, Folder 2)